A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.33 (A2007) FA492
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2007.042: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2006; AC.2007.042; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3851, R3852.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2007.042.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 98023 #45 - PAN AMERICAN HEALTH ORGANIZATION - PUBLIC HEALTH EDUCATION, 2000-2005 (Box R3852)
    - RF 98024 #90 - CHINESE UNIVERSITY OF HONG KONG - SCHERING NETWORK POSTDOC PROJECT, 1998-2004 (Box R3852)
- AC.2007.051: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1978-2005; AC.2007.051; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3853, R3854.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2007.051.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 98001 #664 - CHUNGBUK NATIONAL UNIVERSITY - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR CHO YONG GU, 1997-2003 (Box R3853)
    - RF 98024 #93 - BABRAHAM INSTITUTE (ENGLAND) - SCHERING NETWORK POSTDOC PROJECT, 1998-2002 (Box R3853)
    - RF 98024 #94 - MEDICAL RESEARCH COUNCIL REPRODUCTIVE BIOLOGY UNIT (SCOTLAND) - OXIDATIVE STRESS IN THE EPIDIDYMIS, 1996-2002 (Box R3853)
    - RF 98024 #98 - CATHOLIC UNIVERSITY OF (CHILE) - FEMALE REPRODUCTIVE FUNCTION, 1978-2002 (Box R3853, Box R3854)
    - RF 98024 #98 - CATHOLIC UNIVERSITY OF (CHILE) - FEMALE REPRODUCTIVE FUNCTION - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1978-2002 (Box R3853, Box R3854)
    - RF 98024 #101 - CONCEPT FOUNDATION (THAILAND) - DEVELOPING MIFEPRISTONE IN CHINA AND INDIA, 1996-2005 (Box R3854)
- AC.2007.067: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1987-2004; AC.2007.067; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3855, R3856.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2007.067.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 98024 #102 - PASCAL UNIVERSITY (FRANCE) - SCHERING NETWORK POSTDOC PROJECT, 2000-2003 (Box R3855)
    - RF 98026 - INTERNATIONAL ARTS FESTIVALS, 1987-2004 (Box R3856, Box R3855)
- AC.2007.073: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2005; AC.2007.073; 9.17 Cubic Feet 7 standard record storage boxes, R3857-R3863.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2007.073.1; 9.17 Cubic Feet 7 record storage boxes
    - RF 97050 #12; RF 98032 #28 - (EQUAL OPPORTUNITY) - BC TEAM: IMPLEMENTATION PLANS FORTHE NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE PROGRAM FRAMEWORK, 1999-2002 (Box R3857)
    - RF 98027 #363 - INTAR HISPANIC AMERICAN ARTS CENTER - THEATER WORK, "MANUAL FOR A DESPERATE CROSSING", 1998-2004 (Box R3857)
    - RF 98036 #869 - MUIRURI, PHILOMENA WAIRIMU - ACA: GENDER INEQUALITIES AND MANAGEMENT OF LOW-INCOME SETTLEMENTS IN NAIROBI, 1999-2002 (Box R3857)
    - RF 98036 #871 - MBURANO, REWENGE - ACA: GENDER RELATIONS, WOMEN'S STATUS AND CONTRACEPTIVE USE IN CAMEROON, 1999-2003 (Box R3857)
    - RF 98036 #877 - KUNG'U JACKSON NJENGA - ACA: FUNGUS CAUSING GREY LEAF SPOT OF MAIZE IN KENYA, 1999-2001 (Box R3857)
    - RF 98036 #878 - OKOTH, SHEILA A. - ACA: MYCOTOXIN CONTAMINATION IN INFANTS' FOOD IN KENYA, 1999-2002 (Box R3857)
    - RF 98036 #879 - HASLER, RICHARD PATRICK - ACA: COMMUNITY-BASED WILDLIFE MANAGEMENT IN BOTSWANA AND ZIMBABWE, 1999-2004 (Box R3857)
    - RF 98036 #883 - GESAMI, RACHEL KENUNTO - ACA: ACCESS TO HEALTH SERVICES THROUGH HEALTH CARE REFORMS IN KENYA, 2000-2002 (Box R3857)
    - RF 98036 #884 - TUMWINE, JAMES - ACA: RESISTANCE OF TOMATOES TO LATE BLIGHT DISEASE IN UGANDA, 2000-2002 (Box R3857)
    - RF 98036 #886 - MAHIRI, ISHMAIL 0. - ACA: FUELWOOD RESOURCE MANAGEMENT IN KENYA, 1999-2002 (Box R3857)
    - RF 98038 #74 - UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA - MODERNIST ISLAM TRANSLATION PROJECT, 1999-2003 (Box R3857)
    - RF 98040 #71 - WING LUKE MEMORIAL FOUNDATION - CULTURAL PROJECT AND EXHIBITION ON ASIAN PACIFIC AMERICAN WOMEN IN GARMENT MANUFACTURING IN SEATTLE, 1999-2002 (Box R3857)
    - RF 98041 - STRENGTHENING AFRICAN CULTURAL INSTITUTIONS, 1994-1998 (Box R3857)
    - RF 98041 #81 - INTERNATIONAL AFRICAN INSTITUTE (ENGLAND) - ARTS AND HUMANITIES PUBLISHING/PROJECT/NEWSLETTER, 1998-2003 (Box R3857)
    - RF 98045 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY (TEACHERS COLLEGE) - COMMISSION ON TEACHER TRAINING AND DEVELOPMENT, 1994-2004 (Box R3857)
    - RF 98045 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY (TEACHERS COLLEGE) - COMMISSION ON TEACHER TRAINING AND DEVELOPMENT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-2004 (Box R3857, Box R3858)
    - RF 98048 - INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS, 1998-1999 (Box R3858)
    - RF 98048 #10 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER - WELFARE EFFECT OF TRANSGENIC COTTON IN MEXICO, 1999-2002 (Box R3858)
    - RF 97044 #31; RF 98049 #32 - UNITED NATIONS - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION - SECRETARIAT OF THE CHILDREN'S VACCINE INITIATIVE, 1990-2000 (Box R3859, Box R3858, R3860)
    - RF 97044 #31; RF 98049 #32 - UNITED NATIONS - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION - SECRETARIAT OF THE CHILDREN'S VACCINE INITIATIVE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1990-2000 (Box R3859, Box R3858, R3860)
    - RF 98055 #626 - LIBRARY OF CONGRESS - THREE SYMPOSIA, "ISLAMIC SOCIETIES AND GLOBALIZATION", 1999-2002 (Box R3861)
    - RF 99001 #713 - INDONESIAN INSTITUTE OF SCIENCES - RICE CULTIVARS TRANSFORMATION, 1994-2005 (Box R3861)
    - RF 99001 #716 - UNIVERSITY OF DELHI (INDIA) - GENETIC TRANSFORMATION OF RICE AND RICE CHLOROPLASTS, 1995-2004 (Box R3861)
    - RF 99001 #730 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - GENETIC TRANSFORMATION OF RICE AND PEST AND DISEASE RESISTANCE, 1998-2002 (Box R3861)
    - RF 99001 #752 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - IDENTIFICATION AND INTROGRESSION OF QTLS AND HETEROSIS IN RICE, 1998-2003 (Box R3861)
    - RF 99001 #756 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - IDENTIFICATION OF DWARF MUTANTS IN RICE, 1992-2002 (Box R3861)
    - RF 99001 #763 - INDIAN COUNCIL OF AGRJCULTURAL RESEARCH (INDIA) - ENHANCE INSECT AND DISEASE RESISTANCE IN RICE, 1999-2005 (Box R3861)
    - RF 99001 #764 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - SALT-TOLERANT INDICA GENOTYPES AND THEIR GENETIC IMPROVEMENT, 1999-2005 (Box R3862)
    - RF 99001 #765 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - GENE RESEARCH FOR BLAST RESISTANCE IN RICE, 1998-2002 (Box R3862)
    - RF 99001 #774 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - MOLECULAR DISSECTION AND IMPROVEMENT OF NEW PLANT TYPE RICE, 1999-2004 (Box R3862)
    - RF 99001 #784 - OSMANIA UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - GENETIC ENGINEERING OF RICE FOR INSECT RESISTANCE, 1996-2002 (Box R3862)
    - RF 99003 #199 - INTERNATIONAL FOOD POLICY RESEARCH INSTITUTE - 2020 VISION FOR FOOD, AGRICULTURE, AND ENVIRONMENT INITIATIVE, 1999-2003 (Box R3862)
    - RF 99004 - MANAGEMENT OF MAIZE PESTS BY SMALLHOLDERS, 1995-1999 (Box R3862)
    - RF 99004 #44 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RESISTANCE TO PARASITIC WEED STRIGA IN AFRICAN MAIZE, 1997-2005 (Box R3862)
    - RF 99006 #157 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - BUNDA COLLEGE OF AGRICULTURE - FOOD LEGUMES AND GREEN MANURES FOR SOIL FERTILITY, 1996-2004 (Box R3862)
    - RF 99006 #162 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - EX-TISSUE CULTURE CASSAVA RESEARCH, 1997-2004 (Box R3862)
    - RF 99006 #164 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - PHOSPHORUS AND SULPHUR NUTRITION AND MAIZE-LEGUME BASED CROPPING SYSTEMS, 1999-2005 (Box R3862)
    - RF 99006 #166 - MOI UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - IMPROVE SOLUBILITY OF MINJINGU PHOSPHATE ROCK, 1999-2003 (Box R3862)
    - RF 98014 #28; RF 99008 #30 - UNION FOR AFRICAN POPULATION STUDIES (SENEGAL) - CONFERENCE ON AFRICAN POPULATION IN 21ST GENTURY, 1999-2004 (Box R3863)
    - RF 98014 #28; RF 99008 #30 - UNION FOR AFRICAN POPULATION STUDIES (SENEGAL) - CONFERENCE ON AFRICAN POPULATION IN 21ST GENTURY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1999-2004 (Box R3863)
    - RF 99007 - BIOTECHNOLOGY FOR MARGINAL-LAND FOOD CROPS, 1994-1998 (Box R3863)
    - RF 99007 #44 - University of California (San Diego) - Genetic Diversity of Sorghum, 1999-2004 (Box R3863)
    - RF 99009 #216 - MARIE STOPES INTERNATIONAL (ENGLAND) - FUNDRAISING TRAINING PROGRAM, 1995-2001 (Box R3863)
    - RF 99009 #221 - ASSOCIATION FOR THE PROMOTION OF POPULATION ACTIVITIES - SENEGAL - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1999-2001 (Box R3863)
- AC.2007.076: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1995-2002; AC.2007.076; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3864, R3864A
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2007.076.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - LIST OF COMMUNITY DIALOGUES, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - PALMETTO PROJECT, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - PICO, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - PUBLIC CONSERVATION PROJECT, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - SAN FRANCISCO FOUNDATION, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - Z. SMITH REYNOLDS FOUNDATION, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - SOJOURNERS, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - SOUTHERN INSTITUTE FOR EDUCATION AND RESEARCH, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - STUDY CIRCLES, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - STUDY CIRCLES MEETING, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - TENTH PRESBYTERIAN CHURCH, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - ALL CONGREGATIONS TOGETHER (ACT), 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - ATLANTA PROJECT, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - CAHRO, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - CA WORKING GROUP, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - COLORADO ENDOWMENT FOR THE HUMANITIES, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - CROWN HEIGHTS COALITION, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - MARY REYNOLDS BABCOCK FOUNDATION, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - NATIONAL CONFERENCE, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - NATIONAL CONFERENCE - ARKANSAS, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - NEH - NATIONAL CONSERVATION PROGRAM, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - BACKGROUND MATERIAL, 1997-2002 (Box R3864)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - AUDIT OF VIOLENCE AGAINST ASIAN PACIFIC AMERICANS (CBS NEWS), 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - DAY OF DIALOGUE - L.A. NEWS COVERAGE, 1995 October 24-25 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - ERASE THE HATE, 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - HEALING THE HATE, 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - HEALING THE HEART OF AMERICA (HOPE IN THE CITIES), 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - MISSION MISSISSIPPI - BRING UNITY TO MISSISSIPPI, 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - NOT IN OUR TOWN - HONOR ROLL, 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - PROJECT CHANGE (LS CO. VIDEO PRODUCTION), 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - SI COMMUNICATIONS - STORY OF A PEOPLE, 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - STUDY CIRCLE PROGRAM OF RACE RELATIONS, 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - "THE ROCK (WORLD NEWS TONIGHT - WABC), 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - WORLD TRUST - WOMEN'S VIDEO PROJECT, 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - SECOND NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE, ETHNICITY AND CULTURE, 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - EXCERPTS FROM THE SECOND NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE, ETHNICITY AND CULTURE, 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - A NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE, ETHNICITY AND CULTURE, 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - TOWARD A MORE PERFECT UNION: AN INVITATION TO CONVERSATION, 1996 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - NOT IN OUR TOWN (CALIFORNIA WORKING GROUP), 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - NOT IN OUR TOWN II (CALIFORNIA WORKING GROUP), 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - SKIN DEEP, 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - VIDEO - ISM, 1995-1997 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - TAPES - MEETING - LATINO CONVERSATION ON RACE, 1996 October (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - TAPES - MEETING - BLACKSIDE/CIVIL RIGHTS TELECOMM. CRF, 1996 November (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - TAPES - MEETING - POCANTICO: AFRO-AMERICAN CONVERSATION ON RACE, 1996 February (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - TAPES - NORMATIVE LAWYERING CRF, 1996 May 31 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - TAPES - ASIAN CONVERSATION ON RACE, 1996 June 10 (Box R3864A)
    - RF 99014 (RF 98025) - NATIONAL CONVERSATION ON RACE: A COMMUNICATIONS PROGRAM - TAPES - NATIONAL RESEARCH COUNCIL, 1997 March 14 (Box R3864A)
- AC.2007.085: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1989-2005; AC.2007.085; 11.79 Cubic Feet 9 standard record storage boxes, R3865-R3873.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2007.085.1; 11.79 Cubic Feet 9 record storage boxes
    - RF 98020 #35; RF 99015 #41 - UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA - WORKSHOP AND SET OF COMMISSIONED PAPERS ON WELFARE STATE POLICIES AND EMERGING MARKET ECONOMIES, 1999-2004 (Box R3865)
    - RF 99015 - "THE FUTURE OF WORK", 1994-2002 (Box R3865)
    - RF 99015 #38 - WORKING PARTNERSHIPS USA - LABOR MARKET INTERMEDIARIES PROJECT: ECONOMIC OPPORTUNITY IN A VOLATILE ECONOMY, 1999-2004 (Box R3865)
    - RF 99015 #39 - ECONOMIC POLICY INSTITUTE - LOW-SKILLED WORK AND CAREERS IN THE NORTH AMERICAN CARE INDUSTRY, 1999-2003 (Box R3865)
    - RF 99018 - NEW YORK CITY FUND, 1999-2002 (Box R3865)
    - RF 99018 #2 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - NEW YORK CITY FUND, 1996-2003 (Box R3865)
    - RF 99020 #215 - EGERTON UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - SOIL SCIENCE RESEARCH; FIELD TRAINING FOR AFRICAN GRADUATE STUDENTS, 1999-2003 (Box R3865)
    - RF 99020 #224 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME - SYMPOSIUM ON ORGANIC RESOURCE MANAGEMENT, 2000-2001 (Box R3865)
    - RF 99021 #120 - FAMILY HEALTH INTERNATIONAL - EMERGENCY CONTRACEPTION IN VENEZUELA, 2000-2003 (Box R3865)
    - RF 99022 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - PARTNERSHIPS IN DEVELOPMENT COOPERATION, 1999-2002 (Box R3865)
    - RF 99023 #334 - LOCKHART, SHARON - FILM, "NO-NO IKEBANA", 2000-2004 (Box R3865)
    - RF 99023 #335 - LOPEZ, LALO - WEB SITE, "THE VIRTUAL VARRIO", 2000-2004 (Box R3865)
    - RF 99023 #337 - POLLARD, SAM - TELEVISION SERIES, "NATIVE STRANGERS", 2000-2004 (Box R3865)
    - RF 99023 #347 - NATIONAL VIDEO RESOURCES, INC. - "VIDEO NETWORK ON RACE", 1999-2002 (Box R3865)
    - RF 99023 #407 - McCARTER THEATRE - "YELLOWMAN", 1999-2002 (Box R3865)
    - RF 99024 #412 - OTHER MINDS - MUSIC WORK, "MILLENIAL REMIX", 1999-2002 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99024 #414 - PING CHONG AND CO. - PUPPET THEATER WORK, "SPIRIT PROJECT", 1999-2002 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99024 #419 - FOUNDRY THEATRE, MULTIMEDIA WORK, "FIFTH EXOTIC", 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #101 - AGUILAR-SAN JUAN, KARIN - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2001 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #102 - ALIRE, JAY H. - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #103 - ALVARADO, PABLO - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2005 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #104 - CALDWELL, DALE - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #105 - CALDWELL, GILLIAN - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2005 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #106 - CAMPOS, PATRICIA - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #107 - HOFFMAN, JOAN - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #108 - JAMES, TAJ - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2004 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #109 - JOHNSON, KENNETH - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #110 - LANZILLOTTO, ANNIE - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2005 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #111 - MACADAMS - WILLIAM - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #112 - MCMICHAEL, PAMELA - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #113 - MILLER, REBECCA - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #114 - MIYOSHI, KIMBERLY - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #115 - NORTON, HEZ - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #116 - PAGKALINAWAN, CECILIA - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #117 - RAMIREZ, CARMEN - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #118 - SAENZ, THOMAS - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #119 - STREETER, RYAN - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #120 - VAN DE WETERING, SARAH - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #121 - VAN TASSEL, DAVID - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #123 - WILLIAMS-BISHOP, RHEA - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #124 - WONG, FRANCIS - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #126 - LUDWIG, SARAH - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2005 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #127 - PAGE, CARA - NEXT GENERATION LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2003 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99026 #97 - NATIONAL LABOUR AND ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT INSTITUTE (SOUTH AFRICA) - SOUTH AFRICAN LABOR ACTIVISTS, U.S. LABOR ORGANIZERS AND MACROECONOMIC POLICIES OF INTERNATIONAL FINANCIAL INSTITUTIONS, 1999-2002 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99027 #4 - UNIVERSITY OF SAN ANDRES (ARGENTINA) - PHILANTHROPY WORKSHOP IN ARGENTINA, 1999-2002 (Box R3866)
    - RF 99028 #57 - SAN FRANCISCO STATE UNIVERSITY - COMMUNITY JOBS INITIATIVE, 1999-2004 (Box R3867)
    - RF 99029 - ENGAGING THE PRIVATE SECTOR, 1997-2002 (Box R3867)
    - RF 99029 #24 - THE ICA GROUP - NETWORK OF STAFFING SERVICE COMPANIES FOR UNEMPLOYED AND UNDEREMPLOYED, 2000-2004 (Box R3867)
    - RF 99029 #25 - BUSINESS FOR SOCIAL RESPONSIBILITY EDUCATION FUND - BRIEF AND HOW-TO-GUIDE FOR CAREER DEVELOPMENT, 2000-2003 (Box R3867)
    - RF 99029 #28 - WELFARE TO WORK PARTNERSHIP - NEW YORK CITY WORKFORCE SOURCE, 2000-2002 (Box R3867)
    - RF 99032 - FACILITATING THE "COMERIZATION" OF PUBLIC SCHOOLS, 1989-2005 (Box R3868, Box R3867, R3869)
    - RF 99032 - FACILITATING THE "COMERIZATION" OF PUBLIC SCHOOLS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1989-2005 (Box R3868, Box R3867, R3869)
    - RF 99032 - FACILITATING THE "COMERIZATION" OF PUBLIC SCHOOLS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - VIDEOS, 1989-2005 (Box R3870)
    - RF 99032 - FACILITATING THE "COMERIZATION" OF PUBLIC SCHOOLS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL - VIDEOS, 1989-2005 (Box R3871)
    - RF 99032 #108 - LONG ISLAND UNIVERSITY (BROOKVILLE) - SCHOOL DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM, 1997-2002 (Box R3872)
    - RF 99032 #111 - YALE UNIVERSITY - CHILD STUDY CENTER PROGRAM DEVELOPMENT, 1989-2003 (Box R3873, Box R3872)
    - RF 99032 #111 - YALE UNIVERSITY - CHILD STUDY CENTER PROGRAM DEVELOPMENT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1989-2003 (Box R3873)